feverishthoughts.com 2015-03-13

# Privacy Policy — Tricia's Musings

**Privacy Policy for Tricia’s Musings**

Thank you for visiting _Tricia’s Musings_. At Tricia’s Musings, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at _Tricia’s Musings_.

Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by using our [contact form](http://www.feverishthoughts.com/contact/).

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.feverishthoughts.com and how it is used.

 **Collection of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only the administrator of this website has access to this information.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.feverishthoughts.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.feverishthoughts.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Commission Junction, Widget Bucks, Adbrite, Clickbank, Azoogle, Chitika, Linkshare, Amazon, Kontera and others.

Google Adsense has just started serving Third Party ads as well as ads from it’s own network. Google Adsense has provided a list of their [third party ad venders](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) and I expect it will be updated as new third party vendors sign on. Some or all of the third party ad vendors may install cookies in your browser and may provide means to opt out of having their respective cookies installed. To find out which of them provide such means, please visit the Google Adsense list of Third party ad vendors listed above.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.feverishthoughts.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, Web Beacons or interest-based advertising) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

www.feverishthoughts.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.feverishthoughts.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you would like more information about behavioral advertising and would like to know how to prevent your information from being used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

Here are links to some of the most popular web browsers cookie information pages:

  * [Internet Explorer and Windows platform related Cookie information](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies)

I would also like to take a moment to mention that _Tricia’s Musings_ is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, Amazon.com.ca, Inc. Associates Program and the Amazon Europe S.a.r.l. Associates Programme an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com, Amazon.ca, and Amazon.UK.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.

### Share and Enjoy
